And that would be the letter I.
Because I represents your self image.
What do you think of yourself?
How big is your ego in other words?
OK, so there are many different ways in which we can write that letter I, and it indicates how we feel about ourselves.
So there are many representations of that letter I on this sheet.
As you can see, there are various different types of ways in which you can writes that letter I.
See if you can find the way which you write the letter I on this sheet.
So I'm not going to go over every single one.
I'll just point out this one.
This is an I which is fairly plain.
It's unadorned.
It's particularly more confident when you have also the upper and lower bands on it, and by contrast, this one here would indicate a low self-esteem if you're doing a little I, meaning yourself.
And then all those other I's have different meanings too.
But you can basically, from what you now know about handwriting, you can figure out that things like the size and the form of the I, whether it's very ornate, whether it's very plain, that all responds to the I as well.